https://verani.com/privacy-policy

My Searches (0)
My Properties (0)
My Trip List (0)
LoginSign UpCall: 888-723-0306
Property SearchExplore Cities & TownsNew Hampshire Homes For SaleMassachusetts Homes For SaleMaine Homes For SaleVermont Homes For SaleMap SearchOpen HousesLuxury HomesNew ConstructionCommercialBuy A HomeChoosing a Real Estate AgentThe Home Buying ProcessRelocation ServicesNew Homes DivisionSell My HouseChoosing a Listing AgentMarketing Your HomeMoving out of StateLuxury ProgramAbout UsMeet the Leadership TeamAgents & OfficesCareersReviewsPre-Licensing ClassesVeraniCARESVerani Realty BlogIn the NewsContact Us
My Properties
My Searches
Trip List
Login
Register
888-723-0306
Advanced
Privacy Policy
What we gather and protectThe following information is designed to help you understand Verani Realty, Inc.'s Internet Privacy Policy.
Information Collection and Use
Verani Realty, Inc. (dba Berkshire Hathaway HomeServices Verani Realty) gathers information about website visitors to improve the quality of online information and services offered. There are two forms of data that Verani Realty, Inc. collects: site visitorship data and personal information voluntarily provided by site visitors.
Verani Realty, Inc. gathers data on webite activity, such as how many people visit the site, the pages they visit, where they come from, how long they stay, etc. in order to monitor services provided.
This visitorship data is collected on an aggregate, anonymous basis, which means no personal information is associated with this data.
Personal Information
Verani Realty, Inc. collects personal information from site visitors, such as visitors name, address, phone number, e-mail address, etc. only when site visitors voluntarily provide it. Personal information is collected through requests for information, updates, services, and requests for contact. This information is used by Verani Realty, Inc. personnel to provide the requested service. On occasion, this information may be used by Verani Realty, Inc. to request a customer survey of a service provided. Verani Realty, Inc. does not rent or sell Personal information to any third party.
Email
If you receive any emails from our company it is because at some point in time, you agreed to allow a representative of Verani Realty, Inc. to send you emails from our company. We will not share or sell your personal information to any third party without your consent for any reason unless mandated to do so by a court of law. The only people who have access to your email address are employees of Verani Realty, Inc. and you will only be contacted if you wish to receive information, updates, services, or contact from Verani Realty, Inc. and its employees or representatives.
Links to Other Websites
This website may contain links to other sites that are beyond our control. These other websites are not bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of such websites before disclosing any personally-identifying information.
Property SearchNew ConstructionCommercialBuy A HomeSell My HouseAbout UsContact Us
©2020 MLS Property Information Network, Inc; The information in this listing was gathered from third party resources including the seller and public records. MLS Property Information Network, Inc. and its subscribers disclaim any and all representations or warranties as to the accuracy of this information. Copyright 2020 New England Real Estate Network, Inc. All rights reserved. This information is deemed reliable, but not guaranteed. The data relating to real estate displayed on this Site comes in part from the IDX Program of NEREN. The information being provided is for consumers’ personal, non-commercial use and may not be used for any purpose other than to identify prospective properties consumers may be interested in purchasing. Data last updated December 11, 2020.
Listing data is derived in whole or in part from the Maine IDX and is for consumers' personal, noncommercial use only. Dimensions are approximate and not guaranteed. All data should be independently verified. © 2020 Maine Real Estate Information System, Inc. All Rights Reserved
© 2020 BHH Affiliates, LLC. An independently owned and operated franchisee of BHH Affiliates, LLC. Berkshire Hathaway HomeServices and the Berkshire Hathaway HomeServices symbol are registered service marks of Columbia Insurance Company, a Berkshire Hathaway affiliate. Equal Housing Opportunity. View our Privacy Policy
Website Powered by Real Estate Web Solutions
©2020 Real Estate Web Solutions, LLC. All rights reserved. realOMS Login | Switch Mobile Site | Browse Listings
